Juan Sebastian Caicedo Alfonso

Software developer | Electronic engineer

Projects

Port-ecommerce.shop - <u>deployment</u>

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

Massive E-commerce website store. Full stack project, built with Nextjs, React, Redux, Django, Graphql, docker and Postgres. It's fully deployed and implements features like creation of accounts, authentication with JWT, image uploading and storaging, profile editing, email password reset and tag and search engine.

Order Management Application - video

Dec 2021 - Dec 2021

Full interface and restful api that handles the process of creating and processing orders for a retail company. Learned React, Flask, html, javascript, css, bootstrap, sqlalchemy, and mysql. It allows the user to log in, log out, create, display, and delete orders and clients.

Know your business - AltspaceVR MRE

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

Mixed reality extension for the AltspaceVR platform. It uses Nufi's apis to allow users to do taxpayers and trademarks research in Mexico's archives in a 3D environment. Learned typescript and altspace MRE SDK.

Know your business - Web App

Sep 2021 - Oct 2021

Web application that uses Nufi's apis to retrieve information from any company. Learned c#, and ASP, NET as back-end and front-end framework. It uses an implementation of Model-View-Controller architecture (MVC).

Experience

Software Developer - at Encora

Jun 2022 - Oct 2022

Migrating tool for intelligent process development in biopharmaceutical and biotech recently acquired by the company. Learning and migrating technology from the heavy code load of more than 30 repositories. Technology stack: React, MongoDB among others.

Software Developer - at Nufi

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

Developing proof of concepts and new products for the company to work and sell, answering directly to the CEO. Developed a whatsapp chatbot that retrieves info from public ids through OCR and delivers a full report of the people. Developed in node.js, express and selenium.

Software Developer - Internship at Nufi

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

Built a "Know your business" (KYB) web app. Improved the user experience from the previous application the company was implementing. Designed a restful API, which when implemented, increased the legibility and the amount of the data presented to the clients.

Math and Programing Teacher

May 2017 - Sep 2021

Autonomous teacher to students all around the world. Taught 12 students per week identifying their specific way of learning and creating dynamic and fun lessons while getting a student's rate of hiring again of 97%.

Education

Full stack software developer, Holberton School

February 2021 - November 2021

Holberton School is a peer-learning, project-guided, and self-learning-based full-stack software engineering school.

Electronic Engineer, Universidad del Valle

2010 - 2016

Electronic engineering bachelor

Details

jseb.dev



github.com/jsebdev



linkedin.com/in/jsebdev



Profile

Software developer with a keen sense of detail and optimization. Thanks to my eagerness to learn and research I've develop different solutions for the Fintech Industry, including integration of automated messaging services, API design architecture, web scraping and data manipulation.

I like to learn and use clean architectures, agile development methodologies, and front-end frameworks, specially React to build stunning user-oriented platforms.

Technical Skills

- Javascript
- Pvthon
- React
- Django
- Nextjs
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- MvSOL
- Docker

Languages

Spanish: Native

English: Conversational - Proficient